
/* English Quiz Questions
 * creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
 */

let questions = [

/*Q1*/
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which is the best synonym for <br> 'BRIEF'.",
      options: [
                "A) Limited",
                "B) Short",
                "C) Little",
                "D) Small"
               ],
      answer: "B) Short"
    },

/*Q2*/
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which is the best synonym for <br> 'CORPULENT'.",
      options: [
                "A) Lean",
                "B) Gaunt",
                "C) Emaciated",
                "D) Obese"
               ],
      answer: "D) Obese"
    },
    
/* Q No. */
   {
     numb: 3,
     question: "Find the correctly spelt word",
     options: [
               "A) Efficient",
               "B) Treatmeant",
               "C) Beterment",
               "D) Employd"
              ],
     answer: "A) Efficient"
   },

/* Q4 */     
  {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Find the correctly spelt word",
      options: [
                "A) Ommineous",
                "B) Omineous",
                "C) Ominous",
                "D) Omenous"
               ],
      answer: "C) Ominous"
    },
/*Copy till here*/
  
/* Q5 */     
  {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Choose correct meaning of the idioms <br> 'To be above board'",
      options: [
                "A) To have a good height",
                "B) To be honest in any business deal",
                "C) They have no debts",
                "D) To try to be beautiful"
               ],
      answer: "B) To be honest in any business deal"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q6 */     
  {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Choose correct meaning of the idioms <br> 'To put one's hand to plough'",
      options: [
                "A) To take up agricultural farming",
                "B) To get entangled into unnecessary things",
                "C) Take interest in technical work",
                "D) To take a difficult tas"
               ],
      answer: "D) To take a difficult tas"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q7 */     
  {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Complete the sentence <br> I saw a ...... of cows in the field.",
      options: [
                "A) group",
                "B) herd",
                "C) swarm",
                "D) flock"
               ],
      answer: "B) herd"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q8 */ 
  {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Complete the sentence <br> The miser gazed ...... at the pile of gold coins in front of him.",
      options: [
                "A) avidly",
                "B) admiringly",
                "C) thoughtfully",
                "D) earnestly"
               ],
      answer: "A) avidly"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q9 */ 
  {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Select the pair which has the same relationship. <br> DIVA:OPERA",
      options: [
                "A) producer:theatre",
                "B) director:drama",
                "C) conductor:bus",
                "D) thespian:play"
               ],
      answer: "D) thespian:play"
    },
/*Copy till here*/


/* Q10 */    
  {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Select the pair which has the same relationship. <br> PAIN:SEDATIVE",
      options: [
                "A) comfort:stimulant",
                "B) grief:consolation",
                "C) trance:narcotic",
                "D) ache:extraction"
               ],
      answer: "B) grief:consolation"
    },
/*Copy till here*/




]; /* Array close*/